A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Awards in Arts Education Program, RG 7 FA776
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Awards in Arts Education Program, RG 7
1982-1985
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund
FA776
31.96 Cubic Feet 68 legal-sized document boxes (Boxes 1-68).
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
All inquiries to view films require advanced notice of at least 2 business days, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Individual items, including those that are not available in modern formats, may be restricted from access at the discretion of RAC.
All inquiries to view memorabilia require advanced notice of at least 2 business days, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Biographical / Historical
In 1980, the trustees of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund approved the establishment of a five-year program of Awards in Arts Education to identify and encourage exemplary arts programs in public elementary and secondary schools. In a departure from usual policy, the RBF directed the program itself rather than making a grant for that purpose to an outside organization. Between 1982 and 1985, a total of 33 schools received awards of $10,000 each. Awards went to schools whose arts programs were marked by high quality and significant achievement, as judged by the Fund and its 12-member Arts Award Committee. The Award Committee reviewed 1,200 applications, making site visits to 104 finalist schools in 37 states in the first four years of the program.
Three years into the program, however, the members of the Award Committee and the Fund staff involved came to recognize that in most instances, although the awards recognized schools, the excellence that the Fund discovered and rewarded was the result of outstanding teachers or groups of teachers, not programs or curricula that were excellent in the abstract. The RBF invited a group of these outstanding teachers to participate in "A Seminar of Exploration", a five-day research seminar focused not on the teaching of art, but on the art of teaching, and designed to help the Fund better understand how these teachers succeeded in building outstanding programs within the public schools. The Seminar was held in August 1984 at Endicott House Conference Center in Dedham, Massachusetts.
By the fifth year and final year of the program, the RBF found that the quality of applications to the Awards program had declined. David Rockefeller, Jr., RBF trustee and chairman of the Arts Award Committee, said that the judging committee noted, among the general factors contributing to this decline in quality, the "loss of strong incentives for arts improvement that followed the elimination of federal programs designed to enhance curriculum balance; and the appearance of new requirements that limit schools' flexibility to pursue quality in the arts through innovation and enlightened improvisation." Rather than conducting a competition in year five (1986), the Fund chose instead to pursue the most promising opportunities to share available knowledge and insights from top arts programs, including Award winners as well as a number of the runner-up schools.
"A Report on the RBF Awards in Arts Education Program", dated July 1989 – a draft copy of which appears in these files – is a rich resource detailing the RBF's Awards in Arts Education Program. It includes an in-depth look at each of the 33 award schools, including how each school spent their award money and post-award developments within each school. Also included are essays on six of the award schools, written by poets and journalists commissioned by the RBF.
Scope and Contents
The material in this record group primarily covers the period from 1981-1985, when the Awards in Arts Education Program was actively distributing cash awards. Earliest dated material, however dates from 1973 and latest is from 1989.
Each of the three series offers a distinctive view of the Awards in Arts Education Program.
Arrangement
The material in this collection is divided into three series: Award Winners, Administration, and Applications. These three series are further divided into subseries, primarily by award year. This arrangement reflects the original order in which the material was received.
- Award Winners
  Scope and Contents
  Series 1, Award Winners, contains detailed information about each of the 33 winning schools. Each school's file is divided into several sections, including Grant Payment Letter-Narrative/Expenditure Reports, School Application, Committee Comments, Publicity, Miscellaneous, and Essay. In addition, most award schools submitted extensive supplementary material to demonstrate their arts programs which is included in this series.
  - Year One (1982)
    - Fillmore Arts Center, 1981-1986, no date (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
    - German Central Elementary School, 1982-1985, no date (Box 1, Folder 5-7, Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Harding Junior High School, 1981-1984, 1986-1987, 1989, no date (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
      - KGAN-TV coverage of DR Jr. presentation to Harding Junior High; 6 PM News, 4/16, 2016:FA776:001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - High School of Art and Design, 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11-13, Box 3, Folder 14-15)
      - RBF Arts Awards DR Jr. Speech @ HS of Art & Design, 6/22/82, 2016:FA776:002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Horace Mann School, 1981-1988; Dissertation, Mitjl Carvalho Capet, Folders 19-21 (Box 3, Folder 16-20, Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Mamaroneck High School, 1977, 1979-1987, no date (Box 4, Folder 22-28)
      - Mamaroneck High School RBF Award Application; Representative Dance & Video Work, 2016:FA776:003 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - RBF Award to Mamaroneck High School, 1982, 2016:FA776:004 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - "Celebrate...Rockefeller Arts Award...Mamaroneck High School" button, 2016:FA776:005 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Maple Dale – Indian Hill Schools, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 29-33)
    - Northside School of the Arts, 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 34-35)
      - Northside School of the Arts, "Coke is It" and "McDonald's", 2016:FA776:006 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Northside School of the Arts, 20/20 News Magazine (ABC), 2016:FA776:007 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Scarborough Elementary Unit, 1980-1983, 1985-1986, 1988-1989, no date (Box 5, Folder 36-38, Box 6, Folder 39-40)
    - Swain County High School, 1981-1983, 1985, 1987, no date (Box 6, Folder 41-44)
  - Year Two (1983)
    - Base Line Junior High School, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Box 45-47)
    - Bolinas-Stinson School, 1981-1987, no date (Box 7, Folder 48-49)
      - Art Show, Bolinas-Stinson School Award Presentation, 6/3/83, 2016:FA776:008 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - "Lily: A Story about a Girl Like Me", 16 min., color, 2016:FA776:009 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Caledonia Elementary School, 1981-1985, 1987, 1989, no date (Box 7, Folder 50-53)
      - Tel-Ex Call to Ezra Jack Keats, 4/19/1982, 2016:FA776:010 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Caledonia School 1981 - Black History Program, "Black Writers: Past and Present", 2/26/1982, 2016:FA776:011 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Elkhart Memorial High School, 1981-1986, no date (Box 7, Folder 54-56)
    - Farragut High School, 1981, 1983-1987 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Fiorello H. LaGuardia High School of Music and the Arts, 1982-1984, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 58-59)
    - High School for the Performing and Visual Arts, 1982-1984, 1987, no date (Box 8, Folder 60-62)
      - High School for the Performing and Visual Arts: Excerpts - "Dames at Sea" (1982); The Making of a Musical - "Girl Crazy" (1980); and "Leave It To Jane" (1981), 2016:FA776:012 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - P. S. 84, 1981-1984, 1986, no date (Box 8, Folder 63, Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Shaftsbury Elementary School, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 65-68)
    - William M. Meredith School, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 69-70)
  - Year Three (1984)
    - Arts Magnet High School, 1977-1987, 1989, no date (Box 9, Folder 71-72, Box 10, Folder 73-77)
      - Dance Department, Dallas Arts Magnet High School - "An Evening of Dance", 3/15/83, 2016:FA776:013 (Box 10, Folder 73)
      - Music Department, Dallas Arts Magnet High School, 2016:FA776:014 (Box 10, Folder 73)
        "Breakin' Up", "Emily", "And to the Wind", "I Feel Death", "Since All is Passing", "Don't Get Around", "Round Midnight", and "Elephant Blues". Performances by Jazz Vocal, Chamber Choir, Lab Band and Solo, and Jazz Combo.
      - Theater Department, Dallas Arts Magnet High School, 2016:FA776:015 (Box 10, Folder 74)
        "Spoon River Anthology", "Blood Wedding", "Manny", "The Crucible", and "Wuthering Heights". Performances by Mime Troupe and Drama Department. Spring 1978, Fall 1980, 1981, 1982.
    - Blatchley Junior High School, 1978-1985, 1987-1988, no date (Box 10, Folder 78-79, Box 11, Folder 80-84)
      - Music Tape, Blatchley Junior High School, Sitka, Alaska, 2016:FA776:016 (Box 11, Folder 83)
      - Blatchley Junior High School, Sitka, Alaska, presents "The Velveteen Rabbit", 2016:FA776:017 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Garfield Elementary School, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 85-88, Box 12, Folder 89-90)
      - Garfield Elementary School 1983 Spring Concert, 2016:FA776:018 (Box 11, Folder 86)
        "Joy to the World", "Du, Du Liegst Mir im Herzen", "All Creatures of Our God and King", "Rock-a My Soul", "Go Down Moses", "Hungarian Dance No. 5", "Marche Militaire", "The Hen's Duet", "Ode to a Washerwoman", "Fame", and Theme and Variations on "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star".
      - Garfield Elementary School 1983 Spring Concert, 2016:FA776:019 (Box 11, Folder 86)
        "The Toy Shoppe", "John B. Sails", "Song Sung Blue", "Grand Old Flag", "Black Hawk Waltz", "Solo Dance", "Fame Dance", "Birdie Dance", "Virginia Reel".
    - Germantown High School, 1979, 1982-1989, no date (Box 12, Folder 91-94, Box 13, Folder 95-99, Box 14, Folder 100-102)
      - Germantown High School Music Department, 2016:FA776:020 (Box 12, Folder 91)
        Includes performances by Concert Choir, Chorale, Concert Band, Jazz Band, SAB Choir, and Girls' Choir.
      - Germantown High School Drama/Theatre Department, 2016:FA776:021 (Box 12, Folder 91)
        "West Side Story", "The Miracle Worker", "The Wiz", "Music Man", "Music!Broadway!America!", "Star Spangled Girl", "Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat", "Trial by Jury", "Black Comedy", "Oklahoma!", "Hello, Dolly", and "Pippin".
      - Germantown High School, Germantown, Tennessee - Documentation Video Tape for Rockefeller Brothers Fund Visitation Committee, 2016:FA776:022 (Box 13, Folder 95)
      - Germantown High School China Arts Exchange Visit, Local Television Coverage and Final Q/A Session, November 13-15, 1984, 2016:FA776:023 (Box 14, Folder 102)
      - "China to Germantown", an Arts Education Exchange, 2/85, Chinese Language Version, 2016:FA776:024 (Box 14, Folder 102)
      - "China to Germantown", an Arts Education Exchange, 2/85, English Language Version, 2016:FA776:025 (Box 14, Folder 102)
      - Germantown High School Documentation Tape I, Rockefeller Brothers Fund Visitation Committee, 12/12/83, 2016:FA776:026 (Box 14, Folder 102)
      - Germantown High School Documentation Tape II, Rockefeller Brothers Fund Visitation Committee, 12/12/83, 2016:FA776:027 (Box 14, Folder 102)
      - Germantown High School, Rockefeller Tape Log Sheet, Summary of Media Coverage for RBF Award Announcement, 2016:FA776:028 (Box 14, Folder 102)
        Press conference; local newspaper coverage; local television coverage; G.H.S. television news coverage; and Cross Talk with Nikki Robertson.
      - David Rockefeller, Jr. Presentation to Germantown High School, April 6, 1984, Arts in Education Award, 2016:FA776:029 (Box 14, Folder 102)
      - Germantown High School, Original Student Video Tape, 2016:FA776:030 (Box 14, Folder 102)
      - Video Cassette - Germantown (No further information), 2016:FA776:031 (Box 14, Folder 102)
      - Porter Leath, A Secret to be Told, Germantown High School, 2016:FA776:032 (Box 14, Folder 102)
        Accompanying letter dated 10/20/87.
    - Montezuma Creek Elementary School, 1981-1988, no date (Box 14, Folder 103-108)
      - Rockefeller Brothers Fund Arts in Education Award, Montezuma Creek Elementary School, 2016:FA776:033 (Box 14, Folder 106)
        Includes: Introduction to the School; Photography and Film; Creative Writing; and Dance, Folk Art, and Performance.
    - Proviso East High School, 1977, 1979, 1982-1986 (Box 14, Folder 109-110, Box 15, Folder 111-113)
    - Snyder High School, 1973, 1975, 1977-1981, 1983, 1987, no date (Box 15, Folder 114-117)
      - Snyder High School, Item #5 - Scenes from Snyder High School Productions and Former Students Who Have Appeared on Network Television Productions, 2016:FA776:034 (Box 15, Folder 115)
        Includes Emmy Award Winner, Powers Boothe.
    - Wyoming High School, 1982-1986, no date (Box 15, Folder 118-120)
  - Year Four (1985)
    - Chevy Chase Elementary School, 1979-1987, no date (Box 16, Folder 121-127)
      - Chevy Chase Elementary School Chorus, February 9, 1984 and May 18, 1984, 2016:FA776:035 (Box 16, Folder 123)
      - Chevy Chase Elementary School, "The 10, 9, 13 Mystery", 3rd Grade, March 1984, 2016:FA776:036 (Box 16, Folder 127)
      - Chevy Chase Elementary School, "Winter of the Dragon", 1984, 2016:FA776:037 (Box 16, Folder 127)
      - Chevy Chase Elementary School - Drama - Macbeth - Improvisation, 12/20/84-1/9/85, 2016:FA776:038 (Box 16, Folder 127)
    - Gilpin Extended Day School, 1983-1987, no date (Box 16, Folder 128-129, Box 17, Folder 130-135)
      - Gilpin Extended Day School Music Program, 2016:FA776:039 (Box 16, Folder 129)
        "Jubilate Deo", "Ladybug", "Fishing Song", "O Zing A Za", "A Voice From a Dream", Selections from Orff-Shulwerk, Vol. I. Gilpin Singers and Gilpin Orff Ensemble.
      - Gilpin Extended Day School - 1. Creative & Performing Arts; 2. Teaching/Work Session; 3. Nutcracker Suite Ballet; 4. Festival of Sound; 5. Gilpin Overview, 2016:FA776:040 (Box 16, Folder 129)
      - Tile from Grade 6 Mural - Gilpin Extended Day School, 2016:FA776:041 (Box 17, Folder 135)
      - Block Print Hanging - Grade 5 - Gilpin Extended Day School, 2016:FA776:042 (Box 17, Folder 135)
      - Weaving - Grade 2 - Gilpin Extended Day School, 2016:FA776:043 (Box 17, Folder 135)
    - King Philip Middle School, 1983-1986, 1988, no date (Box 17, Folder 136-137, Box 18, Folder 138-139)
      - King Philip Middle School - "The Arts at King Philip", 2016:FA776:044 (Box 17, Folder 137)
        Opening; Introduction; Studio Arts; Music Program; Student Commercials; Classroom Projects; Drama Program; and Closing.
      - King Philip Performing Musical Groups - King Philip Middle School Jazz Band, 2016:FA776:045 (Box 18, Folder 138)
    - Mentor High School, 1979-1987, no date (Box 18, Folder 140-144)
    - New Traditions School, 1977, 1981, 1984-1988, no date (Box 18, Folder 145, Box 19, Folder 146-148)
      - New Traditions School Kaleidoscope Ensemble, 2016:FA776:046 (Box 18, Folder 145)
        "Chariots of Fire", "African Boat Song", "Norwegian Wood", "Medieval Garden", "East Indian Song", "Hello Goodbye", and "Greensleeves".
- Administration
  Series 2, Administration, contains office correspondence, including site visit reports from the observers who visited the finalist schools.
  - Year One (1982)
    - Award Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 19, Folder 149)
    - Advisory Committee, 1980-1981, no date (Box 19, Folder 150)
    - Arts Education Awards: Educational Testing Service, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 151-152)
    - Advisory Board, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 153)
    - The Arts, Education and Americans, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 154)
    - Award Committee Meetings, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 155)
    - Case Studies, 1980, no date (Box 19, Folder 156)
    - David Rockefeller, Jr., 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 157)
    - Expenses, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 158)
    - Other Programs, including Criteria, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 159)
    - Staff, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 160)
    - Public Announcements 1981, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 161)
    - Year 1, Book 1 (Administration), 1978-1981 (Box 20, Folder 162-165)
    - Year 1, Book 2 (Administration), 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 166-169)
    - Year 1, Book 3 (Administration), 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 170-173)
    - Site Visit Schools, Year 1 (1981), 1981-1983 (Box 21, Folder 174-177)
    - "Daedalus" Issue (Administration), 1982-1984, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 178-179, Box 22, Folder 180-182)
    - "Daedalus", 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 183)
    - "Daedalus" - Journal of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Volume 112, Number 3, Summer 1983 (Box 22, Folder 184)
    - "Coming to Our Senses", 1977 (Box 22, Folder 185)
  - Year Two (1983)
    - Year 2, Book 1 (Administration), 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 186-189)
    - Year 2, Book 2 (Administration), 1977, 1979, 1981-1983, no date (Box 23, Folder 190-193)
    - Site Visit Schools, Year 2 (1982), 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 194-199, Box 24, Folder 200-202)
    - Year 2, Essay Project, 1977, 1979, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 203-206, Box 25, Folder 207-208)
    - Year 2, Essay Project: Consultant's Files: Helen Kelly, 1961, 1975-1976, 1978-1979, 1981, 1983-1984, no date (Box 25, Folder 209-211)
    - Year 2, Essay Project: Consultant's Files: Poets Meetings, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 212)
    - Year 2, Essay Project: Consultant's Files: Signed Contracts, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 213)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Confidential material
    - Year 2, Prospectus for Poets Essays, 1983-1987; Robert Hass, Folder 214; William Keens, Keens Company, Folder 215 (Box 25, Folder 214-215)
  - Year Three (1984)
    - Year 3, Book 1 (Administration), 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 216, Box 26, Folder 217-219)
    - Year 3, Book 2 (Administration), 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 220-222)
    - Site Visit Schools, Year 3 (1983), 1984 (Box 26, Folder 223)
  - Year Four (1985)
    - Year 4, Book 1 (Administration), 1982, 1984-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 224-225, Folder 226-228)
    - Site Visit Schools, Year 4 (1984), 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 229-231)
    - Site Visit Schools, Year 4 (1984): Compilation of Observation Reports for Arts Awards Committee, 1985 January (Box 27, Folder 232)
  - Year Five (1986)
    - Year 5 (Administration), 1985-1988 (Box 27, Folder 233)
    - Year 5 (Administration): Press Release, 1985 February (Box 27, Folder 234)
    - Year 5 (Administration): "The Development of Excellence in Art Education in Public Schools", Nancy M. McMorris, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 235)
  - A Seminar of Exploration
    - Arts Awards Committee Meeting at Midpoint, 1984 January 14 (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - Arts Award Committee Meeting - 3 hours - What to do with what we've learned, 1/14/84, 2016:FA776:047 (Box 28, Folder 236)
    - Seminar of Exploration with Arts Teachers: Book 1 (Administration), 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 237-238)
    - Seminar of Exploration with Arts Teachers: Book 2 (Administration), 1984-1988, no date (Box 28, Folder 239-243, Box 29, Folder 244)
    - Resumés, 1984, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 245-249)
    - Report to the National Endowment for the Arts, 1988 December (Box 29, Folder 250)
    - Yankelovich, Skelly and White, Inc., Report, 1984 August (Box 29, Folder 251)
    - National Education Association, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 252)
    - Participants List (Teachers): Mailing Lists, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 253)
    - Miscellaneous Notes: Teacher Seminar, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 254)
    - Post-Seminar Correspondence with The Ahmanson Foundation, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 255)
    - Expenses: Teacher Seminar, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 256)
    - A Seminar of Exploration, Endicott House Conference Center, Dedham, Massachusetts, August 3-7, 1984: Slides (Box 29, Folder 257)
    - A Seminar of Exploration, Endicott House Conference Center, Dedham, Massachusetts, August 3-7, 1984: Audio Tapes, 1984, 1986, 1988, no date (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - Howard Gardner on China - Endicott House - 1st 1/8 of tape - 8/4/84, 2016:FA776:048 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - David Richardson - Focus [Elementary] - 8/4/84, 2016:FA776:049 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - David Richardson - Focus [Elementary] - 8/4/84, 2016:FA776:050 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - 5679 - Sat p.m. - Elementary/Middle - Richardson, 2016:FA776:051 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - Richardson - High Schools, 2016:FA776:052 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - Richardson - High Schools - 3rd Side, 2016:FA776:053 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - Ellen Winner's Presentation on Psychology and Art - Endicott - 8/6/84, 2016:FA776:054 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - 350' of Ellen Winner - 8/6 - on Psychology of Art, 2016:FA776:055 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - Unlabeled Audio Cassette, 2016:FA776:056 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - SAT/ELEM/MID/JR HIGH - Pat DZ - (Beginning) - Tape 1, 2016:FA776:057 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - Pat Drizinski, 2016:FA776:058 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - #One - Case Study Discussion for "Daedalus" - Both sides, 2016:FA776:059 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - #Three - Both sides - then see side B of #2, 2016:FA776:060 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - RBF - Arts - Resources Meeting #1 and RBF Resources Meeting #2, 2016:FA776:061 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - 1 RBF AAE - 1/7, 2016:FA776:062 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - 3 RBF AAE - 1/7 and 3 RBF AAE - 1/8, 2016:FA776:063 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - China meeting #1 - 1/18, 2016:FA776:064 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - Doug Murray in China - Tape 1 - 1/22/86, 2016:FA776:065 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - RBF Ed Mtg - Pocantico - Tape 3 of 4 - 6/16/88, 2016:FA776:066 (Box 30, Folder 258)
      - Chevy Chase Elementary - 1984-1985 - Application, 2016:FA776:067 (Box 30, Folder 258)
  - Publicity
    - Unlabeled Portfolio: Slides, Photographs, Negatives, Contact Sheets, 1981, 1982, 1984, no date (Box 30, Folder 259-260)
      - 11 x 14" black and white photograph - #1-4 (Group of people posing on staircase), 2016:FA776:068 (Box 30, Folder 259)
        Photo: Dana Sigall, 348 Congress Street, Boston, MA 02210, (617) 357-5140
      - 11 x 14" black and white photograph - #4-5 (Group of people posing on staircase), 2016:FA776:069 (Box 30, Folder 259)
        Photo: Dana Sigall, 348 Congress Street, Boston, MA 02210, (617)357-5140
    - Advertising, 1981-1985 (Box 30, Folder 261)
    - Advertising: Responses, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 262)
    - Scrapbook: "Media Coverage": Second-Year Winner Schools, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 263)
    - Publicity on RBF Awards in Arts Education Program, Year Two, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 264)
    - Publicity - Year I and II, 1981-1982, no date (Box 30, Folder 265)
    - Publicity - Year III and IV, 1983-1985, no date (Box 30, Folder 266)
  - Office Files
    - Day File (1981-1983), 1980-1983 (Box 31, Folder 267-273)
    - Day File (1984) (Box 31, Folder 274, Box 32, Folder 275-279)
    - Reading File (1985) (Box 32, Folder 280-282, Box 33, Folder 283-284)
    - Reading File (1986) (Box 33, Folder 285)
    - Private Schools, 1981, 1983-1985 (Box 33, Folder 286)
    - Arts Accounting, 1981-1985 (Box 33, Folder 287)
    - Inquiry Letters, 1983-1985 (Box 33, Folder 288-290, Box 34, Folder 291-297)
    - Sour Grapes - Letters, 1982-1984 (Box 34, Folder 298)
    - Log: Support-Commendation Letters, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 299)
    - Master Logs - Year 1-Year 4, 1981-1984 (Box 34, Folder 300)